<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Blogness</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/</link><description/><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:20:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubernetes an emotion</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/fourth-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:20:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/fourth-post/</guid><description>Kubernetes nowadays is a great buzzword among the software community. Actually, it has been for a while now, but not everyone feels the same about it — especially when it comes to its purpose and how it can evolve an architecture in both the wrong and the right way. In this blog, I am going to pen down what I thought, think, and will think about Kubernetes.
The first time I heard the word &amp;ldquo;Kubernetes&amp;rdquo; was way back in 2017, when I was working for a Bangalore-based startup.</description></item><item><title>Atlantis - boon or bane</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/third-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:20:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/third-post/</guid><description>Back to writing another blog after a really long time. A lot has happened in the last year, which kept me away from penning down the ideas and thoughts I’ve had during that period. Today, I made some time to keep the blog post somewhat alive.
I’ve been working at my new job for the past year and have been very involved in improving the overall infrastructure in the organization. Out of the many things that were done, one major change I introduced was Kubernetes.</description></item><item><title>Team Culture: The Heartbeat of Every Great Team!</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/second-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:20:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/second-post/</guid><description>Almost every organization that exists comprises multiple people with different skill sets, and ideally, each of the people with similar skills or different are placed within teams, to work towards a bigger goal, and make their organization do well. Now the question is, does the culture within a team influence the productivity of the team?
To answer the above question we need to understand, what do you understand by the word Culture?</description></item><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 15:20:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Welcome to my first blog ever, this is also my first ever attempt at starting something that would let me share my knowledge/experiences with the world or at least with the people I force to read this(my friends, or just my wife or my dog if she could read :D ).
Why now? Why did I decide to start a blog post in my mid-30s which for some might be a little late, I have seen many folks maintain a blog post since the time of the Y2K and still maintain it to date with hundreds of posts.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dushyant03.github.io/blogness/about/</guid><description>I am a person who has many interests, just like any other person, nothing special for sure:) Some of them are
Long walks, they just relax me(I am a slow walker) Driving(I drive to my gym, which is 400m from home) Cooking(I can cook up a mean Indian dish and lot more) Reading(A sort of new interest I have picked up) Having a good laugh(Who does not like that!) I am also a guy working in the IT like many many of the people around, again nothing special.</description></item></channel></rss>